vitanetonline.com 2017-01-27

# VitaNet ®, LLC Privacy Policy

* * *

We value our customers and will make every effort to respect your privacy. The following is what to expect from VitaNet®, LLC. and our staff.

Effective on 11/15/2013

-Revision on Return policy, 180 days to return products, 10% restocking fee on opened products returned after 60 Days.

**Information Collected and How it is Used**

If you opted to register with us you are asked for your Name, and address to facilitate ordering and reordering from VitaNet®, LLC. However, once registered you do not have to use the same account again to order from us, but for quicker shopping its best to use the same account each time.

During the order process you will be asked for shipping information, name, address, telephone number, email, and choice of payment method. This information is collected in order to process your purchase and shipping purposes. Upon completion of the online order, a confirmation of your order will be sent via email to the email address you supplied if you supplied one. 

VitaNet®, LLC. is hosted by Inhouse. VitaNet®, LLC. hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. VitaNet®, LLC. automatically collects order information.

Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information in any way. 

**Disclosure to Third Parties**

We use our in house credit card machine to process all orders, we do not disclose any credit card information to any company accept the merchant processing company that we process credit cards with or PayPal If you opt to pay with PayPal. Credit Card information is shreaded right after the credit card is charged for an order so there are no papers laying around with sensitive information on them. We use primarily www.usps.com for delivery of orders and all address labels are generated in house with Endicia. 

**AdWords Remarketing**  

  * This website uses Google AdWords
  * This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the VitaNet ®, LLC website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy. 
  * You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page. http://www.google.com/settings/ads

Otherwise, we do not sell, rent, share, or transfer your personal information to third parties. The information you give us is confidential, and will not be sold or given to any individual or company or organization. This is our simple promise to you. 

**“All information you provide is kept completely confidential including email addresses.”**

**Newsletter**

We do provide a once a week newsletter, we provide a way for you to unsubscribe from it if you no longer wish to receive it. If you wish to unsubscribe from our newsletter, you may do so by following the unsubscribe support@vitanet.net.

**Cookies**

VitaNet®, LLC. will place a cookie on your computer whenever you place an item in your shopping cart. This cookie is used to maintain your account number that was assigned when you placed your first item in the shopping cart. VitaNet®, LLC. will maintain your shopping cart details until you decide to proceed to checkout and input shipping details. Your browser needs to accept cookies, otherwise the shopping cart will not function properly. 

**Security**

When you submit personal information on our Web site, we will protect your information both online and offline. 

When you submit sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - (Secure Socket Layer). While on a secure page, such as our order form which is hosted by VitaNet ®, LLC, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. 

We also use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure once we receive it. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access that are located in secured facilities. VitaNet®, LLC. employees are trained and kept up-to-date on our security procedures. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to support@vitanet.net.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:**

If you need to correct or update your personal information (such as your email address), or you no longer desire our services, you can let us know by emailing our customer support at Support@vitanet.net or calling 800.877-8702.

**Notification of Changes**

If we change our privacy policy, we will post a notice of the change on our homepage, so you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, it will be disclosed. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you via email or by posting a prominent notice on our Web site 30 days prior to implementing the change. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or to comply with a legal process served on our Web site. 

**To Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with our Web site, you can contact us at:

**Customer Service** support@vitanetonline.com  
VitaNet®, LLC., 887 Edison ST NW  
Hartville, OH 44632  
Phone: 330-877-8786 Toll Free: 800-877-8702 Fax: 330-877-8787  

|   
  
---|---
